<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Biggs Stopwatch 3</string>
    <string name="test_string">88:88:88.88</string>

    <!--
        menu
        The name of the settings corresponds to the current state,
        that is: the state that currently exists.  So if sound is
        currently playing, then the correct menu item is "turn sound off."
    -->
    <string name="settings_menu_sound_on">Turn Sound OFF</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_sound_off">Turn Sound ON</string>

    <string name="settings_menu_vibrate_on">Turn Vibrate OFF</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_vibrate_off">Turn Vibrate ON</string>

    <string name="settings_menu_disable_screen_saver">Disable Screen Saver</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_enable_screen_saver">Enable Screen Saver</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>

    <string name="about_title">Notes</string>
    <string name="about_msg">
        This is yet another app made by Biggs—version 3 of my famous
        stopwatch app.  It uses all the latest programming bells, whistles, and other crap that is required of
        current Android apps, but you the user don\'t need to know about.  All these latest \"improvements\"
        have forced this app to grow from a sweet little 16 kilobytes (version 1 in 2012) to its current waste of space: 37 megabytes.
        Apologies for the hugeness of this app, but Google no longer approves of lean clean simple programming.
        And that\'s the truth, thbtbtbtt!\n
        \n
        My philosophy is that apps should do one thing and do it well.  If I can\'t find something
        that fits this philosophy, then I make an app that does the trick.  This is a stopwatch.  It
        is not a timer, it is not a clock, and it definitely is not social media.  It accurately
        tells you how much time has elapsed.  To do this it needs no permissions whatsoever!
        Thank you, thank you.  You have finally found an app that records no data, asks no questions,
        and really doesn\'t give a crap who you are and what you do.\n
        \n
        Which leads me to privacy.  This is your phone.  Everything you do with it is completely
        your business.  Not only does this app not collect any data, I don\'t WANT to collect
        data (that would require servers, maintanance, etc. etc. and well frankly, I have a
        life—and I\'m way too lazy to be bothered with such boring stuff).\n
        \n
        So go ahead and use this (not so) little stopwatch app if you like. If you don\'t like
        it, remove the damn thing! Life is too short to worry about the small stuff.\n
        \n
        Feb. 2024
    </string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>


    <!-- button labels -->
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="stop">STOP</string>
    <string name="split">SPLIT</string>
    <string name="clear">CLEAR</string>

    <!-- toast msgs -->
    <string name="sound_on_toast_msg">Sound is now playing</string>
    <string name="sound_off_toast_msg">Sound is turned off</string>

    <string name="screen_saver_disabled_toast_msg">Screen saver will not engage while running Stopwatch</string>
    <string name="screen_saver_enabled_toast_msg">Screen saver will work normally</string>

    <string name="vibration_on_toast_msg">Vibration is turned on</string>
    <string name="vibration_off_toast_msg">Vibration is turned off</string>

</resources>
